welcome to the dry bar comedy podcast uh
folks as usual it's Taylor neelon and
what uh oh H we got over here who in the
I'm sorry I'm not Jordan Mak but uh I'm
Steve Steve Steve soberg yeah that's my
last name I do my research I forgot to
do yeah thank you yeah thank you for
researching so you're not will you
explain to the audience what you're
doing
here you're not Republican no
independent good first but you're also
not replacing Jordan Mak what are you
doing here today Steve oh uh what am I
doing here I don't
know yeah I'm not replacing I'm just
here because uh I'm a big fan of who
we're we're talking with today and so I
said filling in I killed Jordan and uh
and they were like who can do this last
minute I was like oh I guess I'd be
available to fill in yeah yeah after
cleaning up the murder there you go well
and uh I want to say it was worth it pro
given the guest that we had it was worth
it yeah yeah I will miss Jordan severely
he was a good friend and I reanimate him
for the next podcast it's no it's not
impossible no no it's 2024 there's a lot
of medical technology we uh are
currently growing him in a lab I think
we won't regenerating no belly button no
which yeah might be a disappointment to
you Jordan making fans out there cuz
that was one of the features I loved his
belly button yeah oh boy that was a
weird thing I like a good SE uh good
segue into what we're talking about
today not really no no but it's we'll
use it we'll use it we'll take it um
let's go ahead and see our clip to see
who uh Our Guest is today when the kids
were really young they didn't want to
sleep and I I thought they weren't
getting enough physical activity like
enough exercise I thought they're just
not tired uh so I started doing this
thing when they were younger I'd take
them to the park every day and i' just
run them around in circles until they
were exhausted and then we would go home
and they we would go to sleep and that
was working brilliantly for the F first
few weeks until I realized I'm just
building up their
cardio yeah that was a terrible strategy
all that did was increase their speed
and
stamina I don't know what I was thinking
I should have been giving them
cigarettes and Happy
Meals yeah that is slow him down we know
that works that's dated driven right
heart disease little diabetes that'll
Tucker him right
out obviously I'm joking I love my kids
I I would never give them
McDonald's or or cigarettes they don't
want cigarettes Vapes that's what the
kids want these days that Vapes I think
I don't know I would never I would never
all right folks you know who it is he's
got two great dry bar specials wait for
it and upgraded give it up for Tyler
Bo all right you're on uh I'm happy to
be here alive and well yeah thank you
for Sor all the murder talk yeah yeah
that's just starting out on a light note
that I didn't yeah that was not planned
there's actually been a theory that that
Jordan has uh after the success of his
Dy bar specials taken off disappeared so
the Jordan that you've seen uh on this
podcast was an AI version so uh you know
I don't know I don't know now being the
man that ended Jordan would you can
actually tell us that's true AI what you
uh you know I think uh it's probably
it's probably
not yeah well uh thanks for coming by
it's awesome to have you you're in town
to do a dry bar Encore show yes this is
off the Record just live performance two
shows cool which has to be a lot
is it I think it's more fun just
performing versus recording I don't know
maybe you like a there's an excitement
to the to the recording for sure and and
it feels uh there's some some some uh
some importance to it this yeah you but
is a little more less pressure he can be
a little more silly uh cut loose but I I
realized I do something a lot of times
when I have high pressure shows I don't
know if this is a great tactic if
there's other Comics listening younger
Comics I don't know if this is the best
approach but a lot of times when I have
a really big show uh I will throw out
like a brand new joke just to kind of
keep myself on my toes or something I
think do you do it on you do it on
purpose my first dyar special I I I
threw uh like a a brand new joke in
there and like I did um a Show recently
up in Portland at the at the new Mark
theater I was opening for roywood Jr saw
that that was huge and you know you're
like oh so I think there's a tendy
sometimes to get so in your head about
like you know you're set and and it's
got to be so dialed and then so
sometimes I'll just be like you know
what let me just throw out this brand
new thing and maybe it'll hit maybe
it'll won't but it makes you focus on
that bit maybe more than like being
caught up stressed on all the other oh
interesting and then if that bit kind of
lands then you're like feeling good for
the rest of the show yeah yeah so I like
that I think new material makes me happy
like
there's always there there's an
excitement about it and you're like uh
you know it's it's the tight
RPP I love the risk yeah yeah no net
that's very much operating without a net
situation you also I feel like I tend to
sell those bits really hard cuz you're
like I hope this works and then yeah uh
you know I like it you you going use
that Steve
no play it safe yeah just keep well I
love that I love that bit um it sounds
like you got your parenting tactics
really dialed in there you got you got
some secret hacks that maybe uh maybe we
could share on the podcast you got any
other little marcl of wisdom for the for
the new parents out there oh man I'm I'm
just learning as I go I'm trying to do
the best I can I feel like I had good
examples in my my parents so I'm trying
to take the the best of what they did
and then learn some of the new stuff I
don't know I have I have fun with it I
think the biggest skill to any parent
really needs is patience like that's
that's on a serious note that's like the
most critical thing if I could look back
you go you got to learn how to be
patient but just also have fun with it
like I talk about like when I make the
kids lunches I I uh I cut all the crust
off their sandwiches like the way they
like them Monday through Thursday but
then on Fridays I just hit him with all
the
crusts yeah yeah you don't so parents
don't throw those crusts out save them
that's good bread especially in this
economy right now yeah yeah I mean
stretch that bread dollar a little bit
sure yeah and then this is another thing
that if you kid the kids a lot of times
they don't like the crust but they also
don't like the butt ends of the bread I
don't what what do you call oh yeah I
call call the but of the bread the butt
some people call it the heel okay but
the two ends of the bread I feel like
dad's like that's always a big sacrifice
move as a dad sometimes you're like I'm
going to take this for the family and
then you make the sandwich just out of
those two pieces you really feel like
you're doing something that is a huge
sacrifice yeah you're a martyr for sure
uh you know that's a father's role is to
be as a protector you know what I mean
and protect your family from having to
eat those dry ends uh but I but but if
you need to utilize them a lot of people
haven't you just take the butt ends you
flip them around you put the peanut
butter and the jelly or whatever on the
backside then you put those two ends
together so on the out side it looks
like good bread yeah and you but you can
get away with this when the kids are
little cuz they see the white fluffy
part and they're like oh this is but
when they get a little older they'll be
like they'll take a bite and they'll be
like they'll they'll go oh like what's
going on S not today you got me that's a
genius move though that's great you can
get away with it for a good couple of
years I think that's why why is my brain
not able to think just go like that like
for some reason well yeah we can't trick
yourself though is the is the problem
yeah unless yeah you don't really have
that object permanence thing I don't
yeah I wish I didn't yeah maybe if maybe
with grilled cheese yeah I think it's
just one of those things is like hiding
in plain sight once you once you see it
you go oh yeah you could do that du yeah
that's awesome that's awesome that
reminds me my uh my mom growing up would
pack me lunches so that first off thank
you for that Mom but she would she would
do this thing where she would take she
would freeze a ton of
sandwiches and it would be like a a roll
with Canadian bacon in the middle or ham
right and it would and she would just
have a bunch of these Frozen sandwiches
she would just throw in my backpack each
day and I would never eat them so so
there would be like at the end of the
week seven you know why wouldn't you eat
them cuz they were like partially frozen
I was going to say were they thought by
lunch not really not really if I took a
late lunch maybe and I never really like
you can't take a late lunch in
elementary school you're coming home
every day from school hey Mom thanks for
the apple and the car sticks they stay
really cold thanks to these uh ice block
sandwiches frozen ham that I'm unable to
eat yeah I thought it was just to keep
everything cold I know yeah that was pre
I Pack
era just U so that was a hack my mom
used just to kind of streamline the the
lunch process yeah I could see that as
yeah the cooling of a sandwich makes it
hard you know the trading game was
always big at at oh yeah with the brown
bag lunch you know you're like trading
fruit snacks for the Cheeto bag or
whatever exactly I I imagine that you
probably didn't get Top Value for the
frozen ham and cheese no I was sort of
the uh bottom of the economy as far in
the you're in the back talking to the
lunch lady like you got a microwave or
something yeah did you ever smack it on
the table to get a laugh just yeah no uh
maybe used it as a weapon in uh in yeah
but uh no I was bad about disposing of
stuff in my in my like from lunch in
general so there was just a bunch of
stuff in my backpack that I just tayor
threw a rock it was a ham sandwich no
it's not a rock it tastes like a rock it
was was delicious it's delicious given
time yeah well um I really enjoy that
that bit how old are your kids they are
now 11 and 8 wow so yeah time flies and
they're they're getting big and it's
just like every every step uh it's you
know once you you you get these little
these little eras where you think you're
like oh I got this handled I know how to
parent uh an 8-year-old and then as soon
as you start to get a handle on that
then they throw you Cur like something
changes they they hit like a new stage
of development or right and and then
you're learning how to parent a
9-year-old or a 10-year-old are you
feeling like you get you're figuring it
out with 11-year-old and then you're
able to use that what you remember what
you learned on the younger sibling
absolutely
not are they just that different or yeah
I I I can only imagine like every kid
that's what's so mind-boggling as a
parent because you're like I'm I'm
talking to my wife like okay like
arguably we're parenting these kids the
same way like as far as our you know our
kind of house rules and how we approach
but they're just they're so different
but that's just their personality so you
got to parent you know I got to parent
my son a little different than I got to
parent my daughter cuz they're just
different people and uh yeah but it's
fun it's like uh a never ending puzzle
well uh Tyler so you uh you're from
Oregon Washington uh Portland Oregon
Portland Oregon born and raised I
bounced around a little bit um moved to
Boston in 2006 and was there from like
2006 to um 2011 my wife was going to
grad school and we stayed a little extra
and then we moved out to LA I was in
Burbank for like 5 years and then moved
back to Portland so bounced around a bit
oh cool cool so picked up a little
little East Coast got to experience some
some East Coast Winters and Summers and
all that and then and then La the land
of sun and traffic yeah yeah I I'm
actually from Battleground Washington oh
you're super close get out of here yeah
did you that's I didn't know that wait
maybe I did well you're from Washington
M yeah whoa yeah this just happened by
accident pnw yeah a bunch of Pacific
Northwest Brethren we're all we are all
kind of wearing a similar we got a
similar thing going this is a very
Pacific northwesty look like earthy
cones
everybody's yeah yeah we're that's it
interesting I was wondering even the
shoes even the shoes unshaved faces
that's Pacific Northwest oh wow I'm just
not it's kind of freaking me out now
that is weird you you guys how how new
is the beard uh or or is this like a
long time mine's newer not I mean not
that new but only a few
years pretty much uh probably I've had a
beard cons I kind of just grow it out
shave it go it out and shave it but I've
had beer for the last three years
probably okay consistently pandemic
thing yeah pandemic I never even tried
before that really yeah I just uh yeah I
never tried and then uh pandemic hit and
you're like I think we all I don't know
if we were trying or we were not trying
but you're like this is happening yeah
uh for sure but now every now and then
I'll sort of threaten to shave it and my
wife's like
don't very
plainly I'm like do you are you she's
like but you could like grow back right
and I I love her and I want to keep her
so cuz then you you could do one of
those videos of uh your kids reacting to
it that's what's crazy is my kids are
young enough that like that I to me it's
like it's it's a newer thing like it
took no joke probably a year or two
where I would look in the mirror and it
wouldn't I wouldn't be like who's that
yeah now now I look in and it feels
normal but I've got
photos uh from pre beard and my kids
will be like oh like that was so long
ago you didn't even have a beard and I'm
like that's most of my life so it's I I
think they would if I if I shaved it and
I like came home this weekend with no
beard they'd be like what so you haven't
shaved it since Co since you grew it out
after Co or no wow I'll like I've
trimmed it down when I first grew it I
did kind of a uh I had I I let the chin
go long so it was kind of long which was
weird and then at one point I trimmed
the sides real short and kind of had um
I was kind of thinking like what do they
call it like a the Van Dyk where you
have like the the thick mustache and
then the the the chin beard but I kind
of looked kind of looked like uh
uh like cholo
gangster I don't know if like you know
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah if you're
doing too much yeah I always go short I
always keep it pretty short because I
don't want I don't know too long I get I
get scared mine doesn't grow as it it
starts to be like scraggly M you're like
all right that's gross yeah when I shave
mine because I I've shaved it a few
times and uh my mouth just looks so
tiny without my without expect you to
say that no you've never heard this what
I'm at least talked to one person about
this where they shave their their beard
and then they're like where'd my mouth
go oh interesting it's like yeah so I
never thought I had a small mouth until
I shaved after having a beard and it's
like it's a you go dang it for most guys
I I have never heard that for most guys
it's like they're like oh my jawline and
my chin are gone that is gone too so you
add that to the with the no mouth
syndrome you go to a dentist do they do
you find them they're searching they
like so roomy in here with the beard
yeah with a beard your mouth is great
but man please don't shave before your
appointment otherwise I can't find it
man uh I hope it's just like a forc
perspective type thing and not it
actually does shrink a little bit that
that freak me out could you pleasee open
a little wider no and get like I can't
it's a condition I
shaved I'll come back after five yeah
yeah
yeah um well that's interesting beard
I'll uh Pacific Northwest guys beards
College shirts I Al feel like there was
a weird there was a moment where I think
I would I kind of was looking at both of
you and I was like I feel like there's
something familiar or there's oh with
like either way we were dressed or
something and then when we acknowledged
it I was like oh yeah that is what it is
I sensed that do we all have the same
color eyes too no we don't no we're
getting into we're getting back into
conspiracy theories Ty got those we have
small mouths too when we
shave super tiny mouth y so did you
start comedy in um Portland then I did I
started uh and was I got my my start
there just for a couple of years and
then moved to Boston so it was
interesting when I started I made I
think a lot of growth and progress in in
my years in Boston I love the scene
there uh and so then I would get out and
I'd be working clubs and traveling
around and people be like oh you're a
Boston guy and I never felt comfortable
claiming that cuz Boston like people in
Boston are like yeah you know they're
very like you hear it in their to their
neighborhoods too like where are you
from South are you from the North End
like where are you from like I lived in
Charlestown but I I'm not from
Charlestown so it was weird when uh
there was a lot of comics and other
comedians that knew me as like a Boston
guy and I was like I'd always be like
Portland and then I when I moved from
Portland to Boston I always like forgot
about Portland Maine so people would go
where you from and I'd go Portland and I
go Oregon uh cuz I i' like they'd cut
them off before they'd say Portland
Maine and I'm like no real
Portland um but the yeah yeah the re you
know the populated one yeah but yeah I
used to tell people I was from
Washington and they would
say I swear they would oh DC the state
capital yeah very or the not the state
the country country's capital very cool
it's like and I was always a little bit
hurt by that yeah you can't any anywhere
outside the US if you say Washington
they I don't know well that's I just
realized this I never really thought
about that but that's how I think why so
frequently people say Washington State
yes they'll be like I'm from Washington
State to differentiate between
Washington DC but nobody goes I'm from
Iowa State yeah I'm from Delaware state
that sounds like a college at that point
and not a Steve soberg Delaware State
yeah that's that's true yeah here here's
a weird you asked me about hot takes
before we sure uh I don't know if this
is a hot take or just a a confession of
all of the states I I frequently forget
that West Virginia is a state I think
it's the most forgettable state and if
you're from West Virginia I apologize
and I'm sorry I just feel that all the
other Twin States that's what I call
them the twin like it's there's a
there's a there's a counterpart Part
North Dakota South Dakota North Carolina
South Carolina uh and
then West Virginia like Virginia is just
like I'm the real Virginia it's not East
Virginia it's just it's Virginia and
then West Virginia is like Hey we're
weird yeah I don't know I wonder if West
Virginia was at at any point was ever
like hey Virginia like maybe could you
maybe like put a East
like on the front like we could be and
Virginia's like nah n we want to be the
OG yeah I mean you can be West Virginia
but we're Virginia okay yeah and I
wonder if people from West Virginia have
a strong sense of like State identity
compared to like oh you're from like
they get mad if you confuse them with
being actually from Virginia they're
like west side yeah if you live in the
western part of Virginia do people say
like I live in like West Virginia and
they go West Virginia you go no sorry
the Western Western Virginia this is
it's something me for years West
Virginia as well as New
Mexicans yeah people from New Mexico I
turns out you don't never say what I
just said New Mexicans yeah it feels
like that's wrong when I is that what is
that the uh the term for people from
that uh New Mexican new mexic New
Mexicans uh yeah yeah it is yeah it must
be new meites
yeah does uh do people from Mexico get a
little bit mad about that they're like
you think you're the up you think you're
the upgraded version of
us yeah see that was a smart sell on New
Mexico's part instead of saying North
Mexico right they were like let's
actually call it new but I think OG
Mexico still has a lot of strength like
yes people don't you never see a cruise
ship going to New Mexico and I think
that's
there's reasons for that I I think
there's you know other than the landlock
nness I think it's also there's other
reasons also New Mexico I think they
tend to
use high fructose corn syrup whereas
regular Mexico uses the cane sugar yeah
there you go that's why you want to be
down in real Mexico is that just with
the coke right yeah no one wants a new
Mexican Coke
geez it's garbage I went to uh I was in
Tucson and I got and we went to a
Mexican restaurant you'd expect great
Mexican food in Tucson and uh we go to
this Mexican restaurant and realizing
wasn't Mexican it was new Mexican style
cuisine is that what it said yeah which
is sort of like TexMex you know okay
which I'm not a big fan of TexMex
because they just make everything
unnecessarily sweet I feel like yeah
yeah so I prefer that Mexican thing any
high fructose there you go we're all
getting some hot takes in here today
maybe like I don't know why I like a
lukewarm yeah that's a lukewarm T that
was the weakest snap
ever um that's a great hot take I
appreciate that one you came locked and
loaded with that the West virginas are
going to be in the comments section just
like yeah yeah blowing it up that's too
funny um so you're talking about being
on the road do for when you were in
Boston based out of Boston be on the
road is there any uh like worst gig or
craziest
um show that you can remember from that
era or or past it the the worst gig that
I ever did and I've I feel like I've
probably told this story before on a
podcast because it's a frequently Asked
question I did a show in Dickinson North
Dakota I was working with a buddy Keith
Nelson who is one of my longest comedy
buddies he was headlining I was
featuring and we did this
show in this bar and it was probably 90%
dudes that had just come off like the
oil fields uh real rough neck you know
Blue C guys they'd come they'd get off
work and they'd go to this bar and they
would start drinking and they didn't
start the show it was like a late show
it started at like I don't know 9 or 10
but I feel like everyone in the audience
had been there drinking since probably 5
so they're primed and ready to go and I
knew it was a Rowdy room coming in I go
up as soon as I get on stage the
cocktail server comes up with with like
three shots of the three what's called
yeah three the three wise men right Jim
Beam Jack Daniels and Jose quvo and
they're like shots shots shot like
they're peer pressuring me and the oil
men yes and I was like I got to do 35
minutes this was like back I think this
was a triple gig maybe I don't know man
but it's like just two Comics opener
does 35 headliner does an hour and um I
just as soon as I started my set they
were just hackling and I felt like I was
in rare form I was just firing back I
was handling all the hecklers and uh but
it was a it was uh a very rowdy crowd
Keith gets up he's struggling through
his set and towards the end of his Set
uh this guy uh we got to keep it clean
yells some obscenities at him and asks
him to essentially uh uh shut up and
Keith go uh talks to the guy and said
well you know I'm actually I just have
about 15 minutes left I'm actually
getting paid to talk so I'm I'm not
going to shut up but uh his date this
guy's datee his girlfriend or I don't
know if it's his wife or whatever was
also not she was talking through the
whole show and Keith was like if you
could stop talking and if she could stop
talking then I could finish and then the
guy got up and he threw uh his cup at
Keith but it was like a plastic cup and
it didn't have any weight to it so it
didn't really go anywhere and Keith was
like what the heck and then the guy
picks up a glass Bud Light bottle and
chucked it in him and for people that
don't get on stage the lights often are
in your eyes so you really can't see too
much past the first row so Keith didn't
see this bottle till like the last
second and he kind of like turns his
head and it hits him in the side of the
head and it didn't break which was I
don't know if that's worse or better
yeah uh but then Keith dropped the mic
and came running off the stage and I was
coming running over from the bar because
I was like uhoh we're gonna I thought it
was going to be like like you had
benches cleared at a comedy show yeah
this is amazing and I'm not I'm not a
big dude I do you know Keith Nelson uhuh
he's he's an he's an older guy uh but
he's he's like a track in a basketball
he's like he's 67 real lean real thin
but he's a big dude and this guy was
like maybe as tall as him but huge and I
just thought oh I guess we're we're both
getting beat up but you know when you
have a friend and you're like if he's
fighting I'm fighting that's amazing
anyway luckily they had security there
and the security got in front of the guy
and I kind of grabbed Keith so it didn't
come to blows but they took the guy out
Keith finished his show and he's like
bleeding down the side of his head and
what was crazy is that I thought we were
going to have to fight everybody in
there cuz you know you go to these small
towns and you're like everybody knows
everybody they all work together and it
was the funniest thing so we finished
the show Keith finishes the show like a
champ and we go to the up to the bar
afterwards and all the other guys come
up and they're like dude we cannot stand
that guy he's the worst they're like
he's the foreman but we all hate him cu
the only reason he's a foreman is cuz
his dad like owns the company he's not
like a real like he didn't come up in
the trenches uh working on the oil rigs
like the rest of us they're like man if
he would have laid a finger on you we
would have beat the snot nobody likes
him and we Keith was like the hero of
the night oh my gosh so people were
trying to buy us drinks and stuff like
that and we're he's like I want a
Tylenol and a bandit cuz he was like
bleeding but uh yeah that was one of
those shows where I mean and it wasn't
even that I didn't get beaned but still
it was crazy where you're like oh uh we
we probably shouldn't be throwing glass
bottles of people that's uh shows it's
like the absolute vision of everybody's
worst show is you had something thrown
at you because not yeah people heckling
whatever but like heckling to the point
where they're throwing bottles that's
insane yeah also cool that you were like
yep I'm fighting too I I don't think
I've had to have that thought in my
brain since like high school yeah and so
like when you said you know how you if
they fight you fight I was like yeah I
guess so I forgot how that goes yeah I
mean you're right that's the right
answer now there are some there are I
think I've also worked with other Comics
I I I did a show a show one time that
was fine for me but was terrible for
another comic and he got into it with
the audience and they were about ready
to fight him and he kind of was looking
at the other comedians like come on guys
and they're like and yeah and he was
being awful to the crowd so I was kind
of like whatever happens you kind of
deserve it and yeah I do think that
within the world of Comedy there ISS
there is a kinship but to a degree cuz
I've worked with you with people that
are if they're being terrible you go
well I don't have your back but this was
years ago Keith's a really good he's
he's one of my best uh most dearest
friends so I'm not going to just watch
him get into a fight and just sit at the
burn go get him Keith you got this give
it a college try yeah also at this point
like I said I thought it was going to be
us against the entire room so I thought
and just and a room full of blue
collar oh there was yeah there was no
winning those were some hard hands yeah
yeah it was like
well yeah wow that's scary I feel like
you were in Boston during the like for
me Boston had some years where it was
like so many good Comics coming out of
Boston and I like Patrice O'Neal and
Gary Goldman and uh Bill Burr and like
were you there during that uh season
Patrice and uh Bill Burr had already
left for New York when I got there um
but yeah there's so many amazing Comics
who've come out of Boston and also just
like the the number I mean like in late
night when you think about at one point
you had Conan Leno Jimmy Fallon like all
these are all people who've made their
way through Boston and come out of
Boston so there's like a there's a
history of incredible writers and
performers that have come out of that
City so just being there you feel that
it's palpable like Gary Goldman was was
there and he was around when I when I
was there and he's he's one of the best
I mean just I admire his he's so funny
and so thorough like when he's whatever
he talks about you're just like well
that subject's done yeah yeah for sure
yeah yeah he doesn't he have a whole
like he has a whole special on cookies
right my point like J is one of the
alltime greatest yeah yeah it's and to I
love the I love people being able to
make funny out of stuff that it's like
that's not that funny or whatever and
they're like I found it you know uh I
think do you find yourself when you're
looking for bits are you trying to do
that type of uh cuz your bits seem to be
they're true to your life but they're
not I'm like oh here comes Tyler with
the typical you know men and women are
different you know it's like you're
hitting different subjects you're
talking about your kids you're talking
about the energy drinks and all this
different type of and and beatboxing and
doing it's kind of a funky yeah I don't
that's what's weird about this about
this business or art form or whatever
you want to call it is it's like some
people seem to have a very sort of
specific process and then a lot of us
just like I don't know like if you ask
me I don't even know if
I sometimes you just get an idea that
sort of Pops in your head or sometimes
you like all right I want to do you know
I want to write a bit about bottled
water and then you start racking your
brain about it and you're like how do I
make this funny or where's the funny in
this but like it seems like every joke
and every bit's a little like you come
about a little bit differently and
sometimes you just sit there and you're
like all right what's funny but that's
like not the way to think the thing is
to think about that's like everything at
once it's like how do you it's too
overwhelming and you it's like the
Paradox of choice there's when you can
write about anything sometimes you just
get like it's like the overwhelm but
yeah for sure um but
yeah I don't know sometimes you have
just like these little Sparks of I mean
that's going to sound arrogant to say
like little Sparks of Brilliance but I
just mean like sometimes something will
fire and you're like oh like um in this
last special this bit that I really
enjoyed doing and and and working on is
the this the bit I have about EES
dropping and it's one of those things
it's like I've always done and it's such
a mundane that's the thing about comedy
like you can talk about you know big
hilar like I don't know things like
relationships and dating and like or
like have the craziest story but the
craziest night in your life or you can
do like you can find a bit about
shoelaces that people are just like dude
that's hilarious that's the bid and
you're like shoelaces it's so mundane
but this bit about eavesdropping has
been fun because it's so personal it's
so true uh and and also I feel like so
many people it resonates with like
people have come up to me after show and
they're like oh my gosh that's me I
can't shut it off I'm always like
listening to other people they'll be
like oh my you know women will come up
my husband and I go out to eat to dinner
and the whole time I'm just listening to
like the next table over or like that's
what we do together as we like and I'm
like yeah it's just it's really hit with
people and it's fun to see
and uh what a funny thing to do together
to be like we're together let's hear
everyone else I get the joy of it yeah
you're like what do you got over there
I'm over here these people are breaking
up what do you got over there you're
like oh this is like yeah so if you see
me out and about I'm listening just know
that yeah yeah I going to know man you
ever tempted to buy a like a hearing aid
a little prematurely and just like crank
it all the way up
um that I never thought about that
that's a that's a but that would be that
would be a problem CU I'm already
listening enough and my I don't know if
I have standard hearing or better
hearing my eyes aren't good so that'd be
nice if I had like uh super better
hearing but I I do uh I I think part of
it like a focus issue it's like I
remember when I first started dating my
wife like we'd go out on dates and I'd
be so aware of like there's TVs
everywhere and ever since flat screens
like here's a hot take I don't love flat
screens because they're
so uh they're so thin they can put them
anywhere and then they do and they we
don't need TVs everywhere I don't need a
TV at the gas pump yeah TV
go why and I think part of it is they
just go cuz we can it's we put one here
they're cheap enough now like I remember
the first time I saw that I was just
like no not like we're handling highly
flammable chemicals and the last thing
you want is like maybe we should be more
distracted and then you see like YouTube
videos of people getting robbed at gas
pumps you're like you got to have head
on a swivel but anyway I got so
distracted right there but if I went out
with my wife I'm like I want to give her
my attention and then we'd be like at a
bar or a restaurant and there's like two
like flat screens like behind like and
I'm like finding myself I'm looking at
her but all of a sudden my like
attention's like drifting up like this
TV over here I don't even care what the
T but it's there and I'm looking at it
and then I'm like oh but I'm trying to
focus back here and then it's up here
and same thing with like listening is
it's like I don't know if it's that I
hear any better it's just that like my
it's the drift the focus yeah no I've
got that too I've got that too majorly
yeah I've I've yeah if a screens I'm
going to watch it which is stupid
because it's like I'm I'm not even into
whatever sport is on that TV have either
of you done improv training or done like
performance improv yeah uhhuh we used to
do this this exercise cuz it's so
important to be to listen during improv
right to listen to your other players
and um we used to do this listening
exercise where you'd sit down and you'd
have uh two other people on either side
of you tell story tell a story at the
same time
and then for like a minute and then
after they stopped you would say to each
person you say this is the story you
told and you try to tell it back to him
and then you try to tell this person
back so it trains you to like listen and
that was one of those things I was like
always good at that and that's what I
end up doing is like once like you know
these people over here start talking all
of a sudden like I hone in on that and
I'm still trying to pay attention but
I'm like I can listen over here too I'm
picking up all the story wow um I don't
know that's an insane Talent yeah to be
able to hear two stories and process
them both maybe that's a comedian thing
I don't know I know you have to think
about two things at once usually when
you're doing a show yeah it's probably
not great I don't know do you find that
translates to your life like you need
multiple things going
on and to maintain your attention no I
think I'm the opposite like uh I
I don't like to
multitask and I don't even think I don't
even believe in it I I say this all the
time like you should do if you're doing
something you should be focused on that
be present like give your attention to
that thing and I mean for a lot of
reasons once though you can focus on it
and do it well but like also from like
not to get like you know woo woo but
like try to be present in the moment so
if you're you know if I'm doing dishes
try to just be doing those dishes and
not be like I don't know I feel like
they've shown that if you're trying to
do multiple things at once you're not
really doing two things at once usually
you're like just oscillating back and
forth between you know you're doing a
little this a little of this a little
this little this it's like do really no
I like to I like to be focused and uh on
one thing at a
time well going going back to uh you
brought up one of his bits the
beatboxing thing thing I'm I'm very
curious is that a skill that you had pre
comedy that you were able to work into
your yeah yeah yeah absolutely so that
came about from well I started
beatboxing in like uh
in probably like early high school I had
I grew up with I loved hip-hop and rap
music and I had buddies that like want
were aspiring rappers and a couple of
them went so far as to like put out some
albums and like go tour and do gigs and
stuff like that
um and are pretty talented so when we
were younger like we would we would
freestyle and just like at recess and at
lunch and I would a lot of times I would
beat box and they would rap and they
were trying to be legitimate rappers I
would just like do corny raps you know
like the best but you know uh it was fun
and then it was just something I would
do you know I'm like walking to school
did you ever like oh I wish I could have
like a soundtrack to my life like in a
movies TV the walking down the street
like you're like I want that but I would
just like do that on the way to school
like make my own little soundtrack like
you
[Music]
know like it's like oh something's about
to happen this exciting yeah we're
picking up the pace or whatever so I
would I just beat box constantly and
then when I got to college uh I was
doing theater and improv stuff but I
also got in this AC capella group and I
am a okay singer
but not a a a like a soloist I don't
have a an incredible voice but I could
beat box so I wanted to get involved in
some more activities so I went an
audition for this Acappella group and I
did my vocal audition and they were like
okay like they ran me through some
scales and they were like you know
played multiple notes and they're like
can you find the Harmony and you know I
can kind of workably do that but then
they were like is there anything else
you want to show us and I could tell
they weren't like super impressed uh
they were like okay well is there
anything else that you want to and I was
like like this yeah I was like uh there
is
a like and and then they were just like
I just did like this beat box like a
little Showcase of a bunch of different
beats and they were just like huh and it
was they were like so they like took a
quick second they're like do you want to
be in the group wow and then I was like
yeah and then that was it and it was the
funniest thing cuz that was the audition
I was at and then there was a bunch of
guys like waiting out inside the room
and then they were like they were like
you want to be in the group and I was
like yeah and they're like cool sit down
and then the next guy comes in the room
and I could tell he was like how come
he's still here like he was like what I
was like I'm in the group now I get to
vote holy cow yeah and they did you ask
questions then like oh I had so many qu
like when you were the on the other side
of the table uh I think I was a little
bit more like kind of hanging back cuz
initially it was like it was like five
guys and then that was like the first
year that's a pretty small Loa group
it's five uh so we expanded to I think
the first year it was maybe maybe 10 or
maybe nine that was like the sort of the
first formation cuz then you got like
two two people singing per part uh maybe
a soloist and then beatbox so but uh
yeah so I had I had the beatboxing as
soon as I started doing standup it was
one of those things where I was like all
right how can I take this other skill
set that's fun and and uh I enjoy doing
how can I bring this into stand up yeah
yeah and that was that was interesting
because I feel like since I did theater
and I improv like I kind of got out of
the gates pretty fast doing standup and
you asked before the like podcast like
what like what was your first joke so
this wasn't my first joke but it was one
of the first bits that I wrote was was
this beatboxing bit which I won't get
into all the details of it cuz it's
maybe a little dirtier uh it's just like
sound uh this sort of how the sounds
play out of getting it on with uh
somebody in the rhythmic uh nature of
that but it was one of the first like
bits that I wrote and it kind of grew
into this like basically became my
closer and it was this hu it was a it
was the the first bit that showcase beat
boxing um and it it was the weirdest
thing like I had this the I one of the
first bits that I wrote was this this
big closing bit that became like my you
know like my closer and to have that so
early on in my career was fun but also
there was a lot of there was some Comics
coming up that were like oh that's all
you have is that bit and uh jeez yeah
yeah they're
jealous uh I mean I think that just like
you know how the comedy it's like people
everybody's running at a different pace
yeah absolutely and some people start
out real fast and some people it's like
the slow slow build so every I think
there's a lot of that in any comedy
scene there's people that you know get
opportunities early on or or some people
that have like early success and and
some it's tough for other people to see
that and oh
yeah do do you think that you could uh
give Steve and I the uh the basics of
Beatboxing could you give us a level one
oh man when I learned I was like I was
emulating like the the old school like
The Fat Boys like
the like all like it's like hell heavy
breathing and stuff but then now did you
all ever see the boots and cats video
that somebody yeah basically they were
like how do I take words and like the
boots and cats and boot like and turn
that into yeah so there's some
instructional videos out there that are
pretty good but um I don't know I when
I've
taught other cuz I've done some AC
cappella workshops I always think of
like different drum kits like um you
have cuz like The Fat Boys like that old
school
beatbox that doesn't sound like drums I
don't think right like a like that
doesn't sound like a drum whereas like
you know like like that sounds more like
a kick drum so I think of different kits
like there's like the like if you have
like different like a beat machine like
an old school beat machine
uh or like a drum kit would be
like like that sounds a little bit more
like drums or like you can do
like like doesn't sound really like a
snare but so there's like different so
like that's one
kid which is different than like you
want to give I can tell that my mouth I
feel like I just shaved like I have a
tiny mouth mouth yeah that could maybe
help what maybe I don't know but while
I'm watching your mouth and it seems
like you have face muscles that have
gotten used to yeah oh yeah there's some
there's some uh mouel dexterity that you
have to like build up and then and
breath control too especially if you're
going to do it for a long time but I I
always thought so because I used to
break dance too I was deep in the
hip-hop game wow in the world of hip-hop
but um I always felt like break dancing
and beatboxing are two things that where
the learning curve is very it's like a
slow long like people would get started
and I'd tell them don't let anyone see
you do this for a long time like break
dancing oh really cuz it takes some you
see somebody just like rolling around on
the floor and they're like I'm break
dancing you're like are you though I
remember doing that as a kid for sure so
I yeah it's one it's one of those things
that you want to like you want to
practice for a a long time till you get
good before you really showcase it same
thing with beatboxing because if you
don't get like workably decent then you
sound like you're just making like fart
noises yeah I don't know sure sure
there's a fine line between or having an
asthma attack exact yeah exactly there's
a lot of other things that beatboxing
could sound like before it sounds like
an actual enjoyable no like oh that's
good beat yeah there's so much stuff now
that they're insane where they're doing
laser
yeah the stuff that the the the true
like pure beatboxes they're on a
different level I did a show in Hawaii
and they uh on the show booked this kid
Pono who is I don't know this was a
couple years ago he was the world
beatboxing Champion oh my gosh very
talented and unbelievable and they had
him open up the show and he did a bunch
of different things like beatbox uh
songs and and like showcasing his
different skills and then before I did
my set they brought me up on stage and
they were like why don't you battle and
I was like let's not I mean battle we
could yeah how about a little jam
session I mean he would just I mean he's
the king of the world so we we just kind
of did like a little collab it was fun
but the stuff that he's doing is like I
think we if it's like start basic and
then just you got to build like first
get the like like a kick and a snare get
a couple sounds rhythm going and then
try to work in more sounds and that's
what's crazy about this other like this
professional guys they're doing like 37
sounds at the same time yeah how do they
can you do two sounds at
once
uh uh well yeah I mean there's like I
mean yeah yeah go ahead sorry I
interrupted no it just depends on like
I'm trying to cuz like there's people
that can like like rap and beatbox at
the same time like
like d like you know you can hum huming
and uh the throat buzzing that was like
a big one like the like that thing uh
but that's like I Roselle was doing that
he was like one of the first guys I was
like oh that's amazing I gotta figure
out how to do that it's kind of
wild I think I just that's not it oh
there it is it's kind of like the
throat all right this is where you lay
down the freestyle
okay no I don't want to I don't want to
hit it big swallow you ready you want to
hit it you can hit it you should hit it
you want to I'll hit it if you hit it oh
okay here it goes okay uh can you give
us a beat for a freestyle rap about the
podcast should we just let's just go
like like a slow slow yeah yeah let's
just
go sitting in the room doing podcast
with Taylor and Tyler everything's FL
feeling kind of dumb cuz I don't know
what to say but that's okay cuz now it's
your turn beats good make me going to
nod here we are on the dry bar pod here
we go here we go here we go with the big
man known as Tyler
B he's a great comedian awesome he is
celebrated check out his two comedy
specials wait for it and upgrade
I liked it I liked it a lot all right
the rhyme with the name jeez there could
be a career
here you know this is this whole podcast
was just a setup for me to do a
freestyle that was really good I'm I'm I
Love Freestyle stuff I hate doing
it yeah that's but I should practice
maybe that's it right freyle with my
friends quite a bit really and we would
always we would always want um the
excuse to do want a beat like you know
we would pull up something like a on
Spotify like a freestyle beat but to
have a be like an actual beatboxer that
could switch it up would be pretty
awesome that was really good yeah or we
used to be you know beating on tables
with like you know pencils and all that
doing the the table be yeah yeah yeah
there was always some some kid in the in
the class doing the thing doing
something with a sharpie and making a
little
show man I don't know yeah teachers love
[Music]
that um well we're getting close to the
uh end of our time slot here all right
but I want to do something fun to close
it out um you talk about energy drinks
in your uh special yeah are they a big
part of your life you do you still drink
them like in my 20s and stuff I was
drinking definitely a lot more energy
drinks Red Bull monster those 5H Hour
Energy shots and you're just like this
can't be good yeah like long term or at
that level of consumption yeah for sure
that's in the back of my mind too they
also started make like when Red Bull
first came out it was little so little
and then they just started making the
cans bigger and bigger and then now they
have like the monster with like the big
it's like a jug with a the big screw cap
on the top and it looks like it's like a
kff yes yeah that saying please tell me
that there's not some kid drinking that
whole thing in one shot but you know
there is they're going to drink
everything that's available to them
especially as teenagers they also they
used to Market him towards like extreme
athletes right which they're never
having that now it's I feel like they
shifted they're like oh Gamers that's
who's drinking these it's it's kids guys
that are playing fortnite for 20 hours
at a pop or or Call of Duty for two days
straight yeah gamer
fuel well speaking of that so we got
some uh I want to get your opinion on
these uh these energy drinks that we got
here ranking them okay oh here we go all
right we got a classic monster on the
screen here uh that was one of my that
was my first uh so Red Bull was the OG I
think most people that was the Gateway
that was the entry level uh monster was
my second I I've kind of gone through
eras monster was my second era um very
very
sweet almost syrupy yeah it's thick
right it's thicker than a liquid maybe
should be I don't know what how you
would describe the flavor on the monster
but uh
always I shifted to the blue one that
was the sugarfree yes definitely lighter
not as
sweet uh so I went um very quickly from
the green can to the blue can but
monster I reached out to them at one
point I reached out to a bunch of energy
companies and I was like hey I'm a
touring comic I'm it's I'm like it's
long drives it's late nights I am your
customer and I am in front of your
customer on a nightly basis yeah I was
like let's do a sponsorship wrap my car
you know what I mean cuz I was working
on the road a lot more like in my 20s
and early 30s I'm like give me a monster
car WAP sponsor me like you know no way
and did did it go anywhere uh I heard
back I I didn't hear back from Red Bull
actually the folks at monster they were
like Hey we're you know cuz they were
sponsoring like uh rock bands and stuff
like that I'm like come on why not
comedy you know the Monster Energy
Comedy Tour I'll drink it I'll have a
can on stage I'm already drinking it
yeah you know uh but they sent me they
sent me a bunch of Swag they were like
sorry you know this is is not a
direction that we're interested in going
but they sent me like a bunch of like um
uh like bumper like stickers and uh like
a case of monster and a hat and like a
like a keychain thing like they that's
respectable
the response so shout out to monster for
getting back to me okay let's see this
next one Rockstar uh again uh I so my
go-to is now is actually the white can
the sugar-free sugarfree sugarfree
rockstar I I realized after drinking it
for a long time the flavor is bubblegum
for the longest time I was drinking I'm
going what is the flavor on the and then
I then it struck me I was like this is
like bubble gum old like old school wow
that's like uh like stick or the like a
pink stick of like that came in a pack
of baseball cards with a white powder on
it yeah yeah like a Hubba Bubba yeah man
um for a while this is what drives me
crazy to about companies for a while um
they they did different flavors but
sometimes they'll like they had a peach
they had a peach flavored rock star at
was really it was not too sweet I could
only find it at gas stations couldn't
find it at like grocery stores and then
it started disappearing and I remember
the last time I went to this one gas
station and I bought like the last three
cans they had or the last four cans cuz
I was like it's gone it's disappearing
so Rockstar if you're out there if
you're listening bring back the peach or
just send me a case it was fantastic I
love the peach flavor Five Hour Energy
uh those those suckers work I mean I the
the flavor who cares it's a shot at that
point you're just they know you're just
slamming it yeah uh that says Berry okay
sure uh it's not Berry it just tastes
like batteries kind of yeah yeah um
little Flintstone vitamin mixed with the
battery maybe but oh man I I really did
like I do a joke about I really did take
two one time and oh I didn't
wait that was the problem I took one and
I thought all right um and I remember I
was was on a trible gig and I
was David trible used to book these gigs
and it was like 3 400 miles in between
shows and sometimes the gigs were great
sometimes they were not but um yeah I
took one I waited like 10 or 15 minutes
and then I thought oh man this isn't
really doing anything and I took another
one and then it all came oh rushing in
at one at one point I was that's a
little scary
yeah yeah I wonder if you bought like a
like a whole pack of them like say 12 or
is there a cap like they they're not
legally not allowed to sell you over 30
hours of energy cuz if someone's buying
that much energy you got to wonder what
they're going to get up to what are you
going to be doing I don't even know what
the caffeine level is on there but I I
think a lot of it is the like the the B
vitamins and stuff like that cuz you get
that or the niin that you get that like
nasin flush where your skin like you get
like I don't hot and flushed and your
heart's racing it's Red Bull where's Red
Bull uh it's the classic that's the
classic I zero sugar Red Bull that's my
that's my favorite that's my I've gone
uh Z zero sugar across the board and I
feel like it's hypocritical to say like
oh it's it's the sugar that that's
that's bad um because there's all kinds
of synthetic chemicals in there and and
uh fake sweeteners and stuff like that
which not good for you it's still not
good for you but I do feel like I don't
need the sugar calorie wise and it just
I feel like the sugar makes me extra
jittery so uh but yeah sugar-free Red
Bull it's OG it's uh it's classic and a
lot of plac it's everywhere they've got
distribution like a lot of Comedy Club
it's the cool I think it's the coolest
drink I think it's the most respectable
energy drink to be seen drinking people
won't judge you for a Red Bull as much
as a monster per I do also like at this
point in my life I feel like if I have a
coffee in my hand like no one bats an
eye but I do feel like if I'm walking
around if I have the if I have the big
monster jug like with the with the
canister like yeah I mean I judge myself
I'm like I shouldn't be drinking this
what am I doing yeah where's my life
going okay next
up lightning bolt is that Steven Seagal
Steven okay we've got on the screen
Steven Seagal's limited edition energy
drink lightning bolt it's got some sort
of Japanese character on it got his
little face in the corner that's great
yeah oh man I think people have a lot of
different feelings about Steven Seagal
he's an odd dude uh I don't know what's
in there I feel like he if he put his
face on that can and his backing it
there could be some like it's got the
essence of Seagal in there like the
sweat like Ry there's a little of a
sweat in everything his soul he split
his whole like a soul like a hor Crux
into all these cans of energy drinks
yeah they take a little bit of his uh
like one hair from his ponytail in each
can it's just like and then you put it
in it just smokes and disappears yeah
yeah okay lightning
bolt who's your dad this is real this is
who's your daddy energy drink oh man the
king of energy the the Market's gotten
so what does it say below who's your
daddy oh energy okay who's your Daddy I
I don't know what the story is of this
if you're seeing this in then uh in the
comments let us know if you know the
backstory of who's your daddy energy
drink yeah we are looking for the father
of who's your Daddy yeah that that can
either be a very sad honest
question or it's trying to be like a
little kinky I don't know oh no it
should be yeah hopefully Mory poic
drinks
this or has his guest drink ironically
drinking too much of that will render
reuse sterile
yes exactly you will not be fathering
any children if you drink that I'm
definitely not the daddy okay okay crunk
juice I've seen that uh uh which is
weird because crunk is like a port Monto
a combination of two words uh I hope
that wasn't condescending for anybody CU
I've used that word before and people
look at me crazy like what I needed to
know a port MTO uh it's a it's a port
MTO of crazy
drunk oh the word oh let's go out
tonight let's get crunk crazy drunk so
that is a weird thing to put on a
non-alcoholic beverage unless it is
alcoholic maybe it's like an alcoholic
energy Dr I think these are all straight
up energy drinks yeah what I love is the
three exclamation points after crunk
that really drives the message home C
drunk uh there is one that's just called
cocaine I've seen it I'm going to the
the uh energy drink is called cocaine
yeah yeah wow I think I've heard of that
you're like well that's that seems
irresponsible and false advertising
hopefully unless they're just like it's
actually cocaine was that one of the
Coke brothers who made the original
Coca-Cola split off and made the just
the cocaine energy drink no idea no idea
hopefully okay and I think this is the
last one we got
here blood what blood energy potion and
that's not even uh that that comes in a
bag like that huh yeah so yeah what
we're looking at is a it looks like a
blood bag but it's called blood energy
potion uh mik could you zoom in and
maybe on the uh this is an an actual
product for
drinking yeah that's a great sign when
on a beverage it said they have to
clarify that it's for drinking this is
potable that that is uh that's a little
much it's a little morbid uh I don't I
wouldn't partake of that it seems like
maybe a Halloween thing yeah unless
they're marketing it to like
hemophiliacs or people that're like hey
are you a court low and maybe maybe you
need to pick me up are you a cour low
and then and that's why they had to add
the four drinking messages cuz people
were injecting it directly into their
blood I mean I got to admit like I I
donate blood regularly at Red Cross like
that's a thing I I try do I think it's a
good thing and this is just it's like
it's too accurate it's too accurate oh
yeah the color and yeah yeah the blood
bag and like even the little the little
smudes uh and the scan code on it they
put those like the barcode to scan rumor
has it they actually like at Red Cross
they actually had these stocked for a
while and just people kept getting it
mixed up and just drinking the regular
blood that would be can you imagine that
someone comes in after a car accident
they need like five units and they get
accidentally give them five bags of
Crunk juice and they they're just like
bouncing off the wall that's great their
blood pressure is still low but they're
very
energetic we don't know how much longer
they will be energetic but they are for
now I think I'm going to create one and
call it Port
Monto yeah I mean that's seems like a
cool drink there you go sounds like a
champagne it does sound like a champagne
though this is a port
Monto and but why not C C at it and CA
yeah little up and down at the same time
portm com combination pment combination
of two things right yeah energy drink
champagne yeah there's actually like a
an alcoholic drink called Port yeah yeah
a p perfect yeah so there you go wow
there you go we created it you using
that I'll use it you can have it all
I'll take it yeah well great that's
that's the end of our energy drink
segment uh and uh the getting into a
close of our podcast is there anything
you want to say to the dry bar fans
before we get out of here uh which
camera where am I where I talking right
here right here dyar fans sincerely
thank you this uh this audience this dry
bar audience has been the most
widespread across the I do gigs
sometimes and I'll go to a place and
I'll go I don't know if I I haven't been
here before it's my first time working
in this little place I don't know if I
have any fans here yet or whatever and
uh sure enough someone will show up or a
group of people will show up and they're
like we saw you on dry bar that's why we
came out and it's so cool to go around
and have people come out and go we saw
you we loved you for a special or
whatever and that's why we're here and
so I feel like the dry bar crowd you
know oh they're the best best yeah uh go
to tybo
docomo Facebook uh or Instagram just
Tyler B that's the best place to find
out where I'm going to be sweet well
thanks Tyler for coming on the podcast
and thank you Steve for filling in as
the uh guest host thank you thank you
for having me sorry I murdered Jordan
it's all right BR back for having me on
and for for busting out that dope
freestyle I mean dude that was amazing
yeah wow it's probably going to go viral
that's well that's nice I'm already
feeling it do you have a SoundCloud or
you I'm working on
I'm working up the confidence this will
help all right but thank you guys for
tuning in uh check out dbarc com.com for
upcoming specials and you know as always
the podcast when it's coming out leave a
review and uh we will see you next week
goodbye folks
[Music]